[Music]
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey,
[Music]
hey, hey.
Hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey.
[Music]
Heat. Heat. N.
Everybody
[Music]
know hey everybody
let me let me let every me hey every day
everybody
hey every hey let me let me let me let
me let me let me let me let me let me
let me
hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
let me let me Let me let me know. Let me
let me let me know. Let me let me
let me
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
Are you
[Music]
heat?
Heat.
[Music]
[Applause]
Heat.
[Music]
[Applause]
Heat. Hey. Hey. Hey.
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
for you.
Got you.
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
[Applause]
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
Hey, John. Long time no see.
Right. And I'll tell you, I'll be I'll
be honest with you. You and I talked at
what 12 to 1.
>> Yeah.
>> I did some stuff uh computer stuff from
1 to 2, went right to sleep and woke up
five minutes ago.
>> So, I'm basically the person that you
see all day today.
>> All day.
>> I hope I'm I'm not a disappointment.
>> Today's TED day. And you know, Ted,
sometimes sometimes when we're waiting
for the 10-minute countdown
>> Yeah.
>> to to finish, I go on what is literally
my favorite website on the internet, and
that is find agrave.com.
>> I use find a grave a lot uh to to help
guide the research in my book, right, to
decide who to put in the book. And
I know most of the people who are
important enough to be on Find a Grave
as a famous person. Well, there's one
who's listed as as having her death date
today that I think people would be
interested in.
>> It's Greta Zimmer Freriedman and all it
says is pop culture icon. Okay. Who the
heck is Greta Zimmer Freriedman? And
she's buried here at Arlington Cemetery
in Arlington, Virginia. Well, get this.
Um, it says uh she was she and her
sisters were among the last Jews to make
it out of Austria
uh when the Nazis were in the process of
of ending um immigration.
She made it out to the United States. Uh
she was um let's see uh 12 years old
when she got the visa. She was 15 years
old when she finally settled with her
family in uh in New York City. Got a job
as a dental assistant
on August 14th, 1945. She was working
for dentists JD and JL Burke on
Lexington Avenue in Manhattan. There
were rumors that the war was going to
end that day.
>> And since she wasn't far from Times
Square, she thought about walking over
to see for herself if the rumors were
true. When when she got there, she was
suddenly grabbed by a sailor.
#me too,
>> kissed exuberantly and just as suddenly
left.
She had no idea that an Associated Press
photographer took a picture
>> of the the sailor, you know, like honor
kissing her, but it became that iconic
image
>> of
>> Time Square on V on VJ day. on VJ day,
victory in Japan day.
>> That's amazing. Front page of Life
magazine and everywhere else.
>> So interesting. It says here, front of
culture icon.
>> She is. And it was on the front page of
Life magazine. And in fact, uh later on,
20 years later, Life magazine called it
the most iconic cover it had ever had in
the history of Life magazine. She um she
was misidentified for years as the VJ
day nurse. She wasn't a nurse. She was a
dental assistant. But anyway,
>> kind of brought a copy of error. She was
wearing an all-white uniform.
>> That's right. with the hat and
everything. She brought she brought a
picture of the a copy of the picture to
Albert Eisenstat who took the picture
>> and um and she said, "I need for you to
to acknowledge that this is me because
nobody believes me when I say it was
me." And he said, "I recognize you. That
was definitely you." And then she said
in an interview later, "It was kind of
fun to be world famous even for a moment
because it was totally accidental. Fame
for just being there." And it says here
she died on this date uh September 8th
in Richmond, Virginia at the age of 92
and she was cremated in her ashes
interred at Arlington Cemetery with her
husband Misha Elliot Freriedman.
>> That's very cool. Although I still think
she should have been buried at Times
Square in a moselum. As far as I'm
>> She probably should have been. But that
this is why I write these cemetery
books. I mean, the stories that people
have are just fascinating to me. I love
it.
>> Amazing. Well, nothing we're going to
talk about today is probably going to
rise quite to that level, but let's see
what we can do. The the government of
France has collapsed.
>> The Supreme Court has handed Trump
another victory in his battle against
immigration. Uh, however, he got posed
in uh federal appeals court. He still
has to pay Gene Carol 83 million bucks.
There's that Jerusalem bus stop attack.
We'll talk about the implications there.
>> Trump's pushing school prayer. Dying to
hear what you think about that. But
first, there was some the breaking news
is that the House Oversight Committee
has uh collected some Epstein documents.
>> Yeah.
>> House Democrats are starting to release
some of those documents and most notably
they released this.
So this is of course um uh Epstein was
born in 1953 and in 2003 for the
occasion of his uh 50th birthday his
friends put together uh maybe just did
this I would imagine put together a
birthday book and they were asked to do
a page in honor of Jeffrey and they did
this and Donald Trump allegedly did this
and I'll get into the allegedly I don't
know. I mean, I learned this from my uh
case, my lawsuit, that there's a big
difference. You can't trust a Xerox copy
as being authentic. Um, you know, but
I'm wondering who has the original. It
certainly looks like it certainly looks
like Donald Trump's signature. And I'm
going to say it does one who used to be
a banker and had to look at handwriting
analysis. It certainly looks and who
also is an artist. I'm gonna say whoever
signed that also probably drew that too.
Um, if you just look at the the quality
of the line, but it's it is fascinating
to see the uh the content of this thing.
We were talking about this before we
went on the air with producer Robbie
about how, you know, like what does it
all mean? Right? So, I'm going to read
it for people who can't read it. It says
it's a picture of a of a of a woman's
torso. It says voice over. There must be
more to life than having everything.
Donald, it's all like a script. Yes,
there is. But I won't tell you what it
is, Jeffrey. Nor will I since I also
know what it is, Donald. We have certain
things in common, Jeffrey. Jeffrey, yes,
we do, come to think of it, Donald,
enigmas never age. Have you noticed
that, Jeffrey? As a matter of fact, it
was clear to me the last time I saw you.
Donald, a pal is a wonderful thing.
Happy birthday and may every day be
another wonderful secret.
>> I would not call that a Democrat hoax.
I would say that Donald Trump has to
grab this thing by the horns. You know,
weeks ago, weeks ago, Ted, you and I
were talking about this and I said that
there was a guy uh
Bloomingdale, I forget his first name,
but he was Ronald Reagan's best friend
and he was part of the the Reagan
kitchen cabinet and he died. He died on
top of his girlfriend who was 50 years
younger than he was.
>> And so there are worse ways to go
>> indeed. But I mean, if you're Mrs.
Blooming Dale.
>> Oh, that Yeah.
>> This is going to be a problem. So, later
on in the Washington Post, uh there was
an article saying that that journalists
had spoken to these White House insiders
that the the knee-jerk re reaction was
going to be that Reagan would deny ever
being close to to Bloomingdale.
Uh he was just a guy, you know. Yeah,
sure he was in some of these meetings,
but we weren't really close. It was just
one of those things. And then somebody
said, "Wait a minute. Wait a minute. If
we lie and say that you weren't closed,
that's going to be the story." And so
what they ended up doing is they
released a statement under Reagan's
signature saying, "Bloomingale was one
of my best friends. He was a loyal
friend for many years. We were close.
We, you know, did this together. We did
that together. Our wives were close. the
circumstances of his passing are
unfortunate,
but that's something between him and his
God. And people are like, "You know
what? That was the perfect response."
>> Yeah. Good for Ronald Reagan. It's
exactly the opposite of what Donald
Trump is doing right now with this
Jeffrey Epstein thing.
>> Just come clean. Say, "Look, I was
friendly with Epstein. I didn't know he
was a pedophile. And when I found out he
was a pedophile, I cut off all contact
and I banned him from Mara Lago. So
yeah, okay. I I I sent this silly uh
whatever this is birthday card, but we
were friends at the time. After that, we
weren't friends. Just be honest about
it. Calling it a Democrat hoax just
makes him look stupid and it makes him
look like he's covering up.
>> Yeah. I mean, look, it's it's one of
these things. Can we could we go to
court and say that he definitely drew
and wrote that? No. Um I mean even if we
had the analysis of the pen of the ink
that was used, we have access to the
original. We still couldn't prove it.
>> But you and I both know he wrote that
and we both know he he drew that, right?
I mean there's no question. And so I
mean look, Houdini, thank you very much
for the generous donation.
>> You know, uh the uh Houdini said doesn't
sound like Trump. I gotta agree with
that. I mean, as far as we know, it
doesn't sound like anything Trump would
say or write. It I will argue about the
pen. It looks like the signature was
done with a cheap me pen. The Don only
use Mlan, top-of-the-line pens. No, he
uses El Marcos and he uses
>> We've seen him use Sharpies.
>> Yeah, he th this right here is what he's
been Yeah, he's using Sharpies. Here we
go.
>> This is what he uses. So, um, so that's
a that's a Sharpie. Uh, believe me, I
know my pens. Um, and, uh, yeah, I mean,
I think he I think he signed it. He
likes the Sharpie because it's fat. The
M blah wouldn't make a big thick line
like that no matter what.
>> Um, I have one, so I'm just telling you,
I know. And, um, the and I Yeah. So, I I
think that the question here is who
wrote it? Did he have someone else write
it? Um, I took note of the fact that it
was laid out in the shape of a woman's
torso on purpose, right? So, someone
laid it out. This was probably done by a
computer because it was 2003,
but it looks almost type set. It's meant
to look like an old book,
>> right?
>> Um, now of course obviously the question
is, and now I thought this was
interesting. I think very clearly, um,
this is the work of someone who is
trying to put on heirs. The question is,
is it as a joke? Like, look at look, I'm
going to pretend to be snoody, or are
you really trying to pass yourself off
as fancier than you are?
>> And of course, the big question is,
>> what's your little secret that you and
Jeffrey have in common, Donald? And I
mean, look, it could be anything. I
mean, I'm not going to name the thing
that that comes to mind. It could be
that we know the thing that comes to
mind, but it could be financial. It
could be it could be about something
really innocuous like you both love
chess or whatever, but they've got a
little secret.
>> Just Yeah, just come clean with it and
then move on. I I just don't understand
these responses at all. I just don't get
it.
>> Well, it's like it's always deny, deny,
deny. Right. Like
>> always,
>> but the problem is that it's not
credible
>> and then you get the drip drip drip
which was always the mistake.
Anyway, um I'm looking forward to more.
Um it also strikes me as like these are
little children. These are like little
boys, you know, little boys with their
billions of dollars, you know, just so
pleased with themselves.
>> It's true, man. Oh my god. You know,
>> and and what's and Bill Clinton has to
be enjoying this too because so long as
as people like us or anybody in in media
are talking about Donald Trump and
Jeffrey Epstein, that means they're not
talking about Bill Clinton and Jeffrey
Epstein.
>> Yeah.
>> Unbelievable.
>> It's true. All right. Well, in in in
somewhat more serious news, the
government of France has collapsed. So,
>> which you predicted you predicted it a
couple of days ago, Friday or Thursday.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, I mean, and and I think
I called it pretty much as soon as uh
Francois Bau was appointed prime
minister. So, basically, this is looking
France is looking increasingly like
Italy in the 70s where their governments
are collapsing. It's been two years.
This is government number five on the
way out in two years. Right. So Bou is a
center. They call him a centrist. Fine.
Fair enough. I would call him a center
right guy. But hell, I'm a kami. So So
like, so the point is um basically but
this is really important, right? So
basically um
where do we even start with this? So the
president of France right Macron he has
to now appoint um he he doesn't have to
call an election he has to appoint
someone who can form a government the
pickle for him is who's going to do it I
mean so um Maren Le Pen says that her
proteé
um he's ready to step up and do it there
is no [__] way in the world that
President Mcron is going to let that
happen. Yeah. Then over on the far left,
the left alliance says, "Well, we're
ready to govern." Jean Luke Min is like,
"I'm right here. Right here." Um, and
again, there's no [__] way Emanuel
Macron is going to let that happen
either. Y
>> So, which leaves him with the usual pel
of boring corporist banker centrists.
Um, but those guys, they all know
they're doomed because they can't govern
because the same thing is going to
happen to them. Not to mention there's
only two years left on Macron's term and
he's term li ter term limited out and so
he has nowhere to turn and that's this
really does make it John a political
crisis on par with 1958 and if people
don't know this story because it's
pretty obscure my mom was living in
Paris in 1958 and um there was a and
basically the fourth republic's last
government just couldn't form a
government and there was a crisis is
also simultaneously going on with
France's war in Algeria which wasn't
going well at the same time.
>> Um and so while all this was happening
um the you know nobody knew what was
going to happen. Well, one fine day, my
mom reme told me, and I've read the
story elsewhere, the newspapers didn't
appear at the corner news stand, and
when you went to turn on the the
television, there was just the males
playing on a loop with the French flag.
And when you put on the radio, there was
just the males playing on a loop.
>> This this is right out of a Soviet uh
premiership death.
>> Correct. or out of like a third world
coup.
>> Yes.
>> So, so three days went by and you know
198 days there must have been 20 daily
newspapers in Paris in in in in 1958.
Three days go by, people are just like
wondering what the hell is going on. And
after three days, the TV comes back on
and self-appointed new president Charles
de Gaulle announces that he has he's
going to create the fifth republic. call
for a new constitutional convention and
solve the crisis basically by kind of
force of personality. So it was a coup.
France had a coup in 1958. Um and you
know he basically aligned all the powers
that be behind the scenes turned off the
media and then so it's
>> not the media
>> basically he turned off the media.
>> It's that it's incredible.
>> But you can't do that now. So I but
Macron's not really in a very different
situation than they were in there in the
late 50s. I don't know where he goes
from here. And the thing is this is a
big deal because it's about literally
the uh the what kind of country France
wants to be. I mean France unlike the
United States has always defined itself
as a as a country that's based on rights
and privileges from being a citizen.
Being a citizen means like the American
Express card commercial, membership has
its privileges. You're a French citizen.
You can retire a decent lifestyle at the
age of 62 and go all the way to your
death and never be sleeping outside or
dumpster diving. Um you you know you you
you can your kids can go to college
basically for free. Um you know, you're
never going to be spending your incur
massive medical debt or student loan
debt. um you know you're protected and
the s and and macronisma
is about the opposite of that. It's
about trying to Americanize things and
basically point to the national debt and
say we need austerity and both the
far-left predictably and the far right a
little bit less predictably are are
aligned against austerity against the
center corporatists represented by
Macron. Mcronone is at 15% approval
rating right now. He and Eric Adams
should be friends. they should hang out.
They've got the same polls.
>> So, this is a big deal. I mean, France
is along with Germany, one of the two
founding members of the EU. It's an
incredibly it's a permanent member of
the Security Council. It is an important
country and they don't know what to do.
And what's funny is I don't even know is
it is the debt really that bad or is
this just all in their minds? I don't
know the answer. I have a question for
you too, Ted, and and maybe you've
answered this before and I don't recall.
Well, it's kind of a two-part question.
Number one, why is Marine Le Pen not
permitted to run uh even though she's,
you know, she inherited this party from
her father? It's essentially their
family party. Number two, um would you
attribute the popularity of the far
right to the fact that Macron has tried
to squatchch them or is this some sort
of a reaction against immigration or
against the growing um number of Muslims
in France?
>> Well, um yeah, I'll start with the last
one first. Um, yeah, I think the I mean,
look, immigration's front and center
here, but Le Pen, you know, I when you
hear that, you know, when people hear
that she's not allowed to run, they
assume it's like her father who got
busted for anti-semit, you know,
basically Holocaust revisionism and
Holocaust denialism, and that's illegal
in France in under French law. You're
just not allowed to say that the
Holocaust didn't happen or question the
narrative. Um and so the but with Marine
Le Pen this is really it's about
embezzlement and it's a little bit like
the lawfare that was waged. Yeah. So
basically um a court found that both in
Paris found that both Maren Leen and uh
other members of her her party which is
the national rally uh misused EU funds
because basically the EU provides
matching funds for uh running for EU
office and instead of using it to
campaign and for the things that they're
supposed to use it for she used it they
used it to pay staff. Oh. So, okay.
>> So, she was she was sentenced to a
five-year ban on holding any public
office. Um, and she she faces two years
in prison, four-year prison term total.
She's appealing currently. Uh, and she
had to pay fill out. I don't know if
she's actually paid it or not, €100,000.
So, she's got Jordan Bardella is her
like protege. And, you know, it's by the
way that relationship feels a little bit
like Ian Rand and her prediliction for
younger dudes. I don't know if there's
anything sexual there at all, but it
kind of looks like it, but um you know,
who knows? It's France. Anything's
possible.
>> Um but yeah, that's why she can't run.
She can't run this time. She can't run
in 2027. She could run next time, but
you know, that's that's going to be five
years later,
>> right? Right. Right. I get it.
>> So, it's a so it's a it is super super
interesting. Uh thank you, Matthew Blair
Reigns for the donation. Um, what do we
think of the Franka Freak? Has it
actually delivered any benefits to
France or is it just a way for them?
>> It's I'm going to answer the question. I
think it's watered down neoc
colonialism.
>> Yeah,
>> that's it.
>> I I know I know a small fraction of what
you know about France and I would say
that's
>> 100% it.
>> You've got you've got Yeah, you've got
Yeah, you've got Greece well covered.
So, and many many other countries. Um,
so yeah, so I think we're going to, but
basically this is about the French are
are deciding, you know, what do they
want to be? And there's definitely a
move towards austerity, like you know,
we can't keep spending this way. I mean,
you could also argue that maybe the
French wouldn't be in so much trouble if
they weren't promising, for example, to
help the Ukrainians out or if they
weren't also uh, you know, doing without
Russian oil and gas. Yes. Um, you know,
they would that that hurt their economy.
But France, but France has structural
problems anyway. Um, they have a very
very low birth rate, even worse than
ours. Um, and they've been suffering
with that [__] for a century or more. I
mean, basically, they they never
recovered from World War I in that
respect.
>> Oh my god. Greece is in the same
predicament where it has the the largest
population decline on a percentage basis
in all of Europe, not just the European
Union, but in all of Europe. And it
well, it started decades ago, of course,
uh but it accelerated during the
economic collapse. And I read an I read
an editorial in one of the Greek papers
the other day and it was talking about
where educated Greeks are going. They're
going to the United States, to the UK,
to Germany, to Australia. But it says
when 1,500
educated Greeks, people with master's
degrees, law degrees, MDs, PhDs, when
1,500 of them move to Turkey
for more opportunity,
you know you're screwed.
>> That is very, very That's funny and sad.
>> Terrible. Well, good luck to the French.
I hope they can pull through this. Yeah,
I mean honestly their big mistake I
think was you know it's the French get
into trouble whenever they trust a
single man. They you know they they
trusted uh Philip Petan in 1940 like
don't worry I got you. I'll take care of
this. I'll be your shield. That didn't
work out well. Uh it didn't work out
well in in 58 when they trusted de Gaul
or in ' 68 when they trusted de Gaul. Um
you know the French are better off with
like a more you know hedging their bets.
They trusted Macron. I mean, they
basically g they put him in he was a kid
>> and they gave him a parliament of all
all of his own and like basically he
didn't know what to and he didn't do
[__] with it.
>> Yeah, he blew it.
>> Crazy.
>> So, yeah. Well, this is one of those
like we'll just have to watch and see
what happens next. By America,
>> that's how I feel. Like 10 years ago, I
remember thinking, "Oh my god, the Greek
prime minister is 10 years younger than
I am." It's like, what am I doing wrong?
I must be a bum or something.
>> Well, hey, you know, the way things are
looking, you might get that you the nod
for the French prime minister job. No
one wants it, right? No one no one in
the center uh on the center right wants
it. They they know they're going to look
like a fool.
>> Yes.
>> Yes, indeed.
>> And the thing is, the French care mo
much more than Americans do about their
dignity. It's part of their culture. Um,
all right. What do we want to talk about
next?
>> You want to do Jean Carol? You want to
>> Yeah, let's do Jean Carol. That should
be an easy one.
>> Easy.
>> I I deep respect for Jean Carol. She has
so much I was going to say she has balls
of steel, but that doesn't make any
sense. She has so much inner fortitude
that she stuck this out. She continued
her suit. The political tide turned
against her. She didn't care. She kept
suing.
And uh today she won. What was it, Ted?
83 and a half million dollars, I think.
Or 85.3 million.
>> 83. Yeah. But who's counting?
>> Right. Um and today was a day where
today was a day that was very good for
Donald Trump in the federal courts,
especially in the Supreme Court.
>> He won pretty much everything except
that. And that was a personal slight
against him.
>> Yeah.
>> So good for Eene Carol.
>> Yeah. I mean it it must have been pretty
humiliating. Although I do kind of have
a problem with the idea that you know he
Donald Trump had this alleged incident
back in the mid 90s. Okay. So
>> how do you defend yourself
>> 30 years ago, right? And how does he say
like Okay, so by all accounts they
hooked up and went into the into the
dressing room at uh what what was it at
Lord and Taylor's?
Yeah. and uh and and you know and so she
said and basically they they had sex.
The question is did they um you know was
it consensual or not?
>> Right.
>> I mean how does Donald Trump defend
himself from that? I don't know.
>> You can't defend yourself.
>> Yeah, it's kind of a problem. I was
asked uh in the in the chat here whether
I draw my own cartoons. Um, I'm like,
look, if I were going to hire someone to
draw my draw cartoons for me, they'd
look a lot better than the ones I do.
So, here, let me let me answer that
question with some visual evidence here.
Like, that's the that's next that's this
week's cartoons, you know, draw I draw
them by black and white and then uh scan
them in and do them in color. So,
>> hey, can I can I answer um some comments
from both Houdini Houdini and Starline?
They're talking about real estate in
Greece. I am absolutely freaking
obsessed with real estate in Greece and
I use this app every single day. It's
called Sptogatoss. It means house cat.
Um cute
>> because I fully intend to buy real
estate in in Athens. Here's the problem.
the prices of real estate were going
like a rocket straight up because as
they point out quite quite uh correctly,
you invest €200,000 or €250,000 and you
get a golden visa, right? So, Athens
real estate
was being bought up, like all of it, by
Russians, Chinese, and Israelis. Not
because they want to live in in Athens,
but because just in case things turned
to [__] and they needed to run
somewhere. That's a pretty nice place.
>> Plan B.
>> What happened was
since they're not living there, they
turn all those units into Airbnbs. I
haven't I can't even tell you the last
time I stayed in a hotel in Athens. I
always stay in Airbnbs.
So, um,
the result of that was that there's now
no
residential real estate available for
rent, right? All of the empty apartments
are now Airbnbs and they're all owned by
foreigners. So, the government passed a
law couple of weeks ago, no more
Airbnbs. the ones that are Airbnb now.
Okay, no new real estate can be
converted into Airbnbs inside the city
of Athens and prices now have fallen
like a stone. I've been looking at this
one condo. It's on the eighth floor
of a building and the the view of the
Parthonon is like a punch in your face.
It's like right there in front of you,
right? Exactly the kind of place that I
want.
It went up to €600,000
and it's back down to €250,000.
Like a roller coaster.
>> So now's the time.
>> Now's the time.
>> Wow.
>> And and interest rates are going to
start to drop, including in Europe. So
>> yeah, that's right. That's right. And if
you're a an EU national, you can get a a
loan, even an investment loan for for
real estate. I'm I' I'd like to pay cash
if I have the opportunity to do it. But
anyway, just
>> Starland, I'm afraid. No, I don't. Uh
John, you told a story about Greece and
cats last week and I already forgot what
it was. Yeah.
>> Do you remember? I don't remember.
>> There there are no rats in in Athens
because there are, you know, 150,000
cats or whatever it is, a million cats,
I don't know.
>> And you know, tourists love the cats.
They they'll come up to your to your
table at a restaurant and you give them
a little smelt or a shrimp or whatever
and they purr and you know brush up
against you. But as a result there are
no rats in Greece. It's just a
completely alien thought to to you know
think that oh you sit down at a
restaurant you see a rat run across the
uh the pavement. And here in Washington,
we're second only to New York in the
fact you remember when we were kids,
Ted, the movies uh Willard and Ben.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yeah. That's We're living it now.
>> Yo, that's true.
>> The the places are overrun with rats.
And I mean, they're big. I saw one the
other day. I'm telling you, without any
exaggeration, this thing was the size of
a small dog. Never in my life ever have
I seen a rat this big. I'll get I'll
tell you another thing real quickly and
then I'll move on.
I was having trouble sleeping the other
night cuz I'm old and I guess this is
like life from now on. So, I'm I'm It's
1:00 in the morning. I'm sitting in my
chair right over here watching TV and my
phone rings and it's a friend of my
father's.
So, I answer the phone and I said I
said, "Jim, are you okay?" One o'clock
in the morning. Jim, I said, "Are you
okay?" He said, "No, my son is stranded
in Washington DC with a buddy of his.
They went into this 7-Eleven and
somebody got into their van and stole
the van, took everything. Their luggage
was in the back, their passports, their
laptops, everything. Everything. They
have nothing. I said, "Okay, no problem.
I'll I'll pick them up. Where are they?"
He gave me an address. I said, "What in
the world would they do in that part of
town? Like, I wouldn't go to that part
of town in the daytime." Well, because
they're idiots and they went on
Hotel.com, hotels.com, and it was the
cheapest hotel. I said, "Yeah, well,
it's the reason it's the cheapest
hotel." I said, "Tell him I'll be there
in 30 minutes. I'll pick him up." So, I
speed over to Southeast Washington.
I get there finally. It was about 1:45
in the morning.
>> O, better you than me.
>> They're both 18 years old and they're
panicked. And I thought they were
panicked because they just had all their
[__] stolen. They're in a terrible part
of town. That was not why they were
panicked. They were panicked because
while they were waiting for me, they
noticed a homeless guy sleeping on the
ground and rats were eating his toes.
>> No way.
>> I said, "Yeah." I said, "Welcome to
Washington. We are rat central these
days, and I don't know why nobody wants
to do anything about it." And they were
like, "We never saw anything like that
in our lives. Oh, I never want to come
back here." I was like, "Well, yeah,
exactly." So, so I I went to uh when I
went to college, I was expelled after my
junior year.
>> What? Why?
>> It's true. Well, when you interview me,
I'll tell you. Okay. It was it was kind
of over a wart. Uh but I think I told
you about the wart story, but I was
expelled and um so I moved in with two
other guys who'd both been expelled at
the same time. And uh we lived together.
We had adventures two and a half years.
Anyway, when we all when it all went
sideways, um two of us, we each had
girlfriends. We moved in with our
girlfriends and then this the third one,
Chris, he moved out to Jersey City and
he moved into this dump that and he
said, and I was like, "How's it going?"
I talked to him on the phone. He goes,
"It's not good. At night, the rats run
over me." And I'm like, "What?" He goes,
"Yeah, there's the the place is full of
giant rats." And when a New Yorker tells
you giant rats, that doesn't mean like
this, right? It means big. And so he's
like, he goes, "Yeah, they run across me
and they bite me at night while I'm
sleeping." And I'm like, "I would be I
would leave. I'd be sleeping outside
before I did this." He was So I'm like,
"Well, you got to do something." He's
like, "What do I do? I don't know what
to do." And so he said he was at one
point going through 30 glue traps a day
with with all
>> a day. a day.
A day. I mean, that's a lot of rats. So,
I was like, "Dude, you gotta go down to
the I'm like, "You gotta go down to the
pound and get like three big tom cats."
And you know, my my mom taught me that
like the best mousers have the longest
tails. And she's like, so it's like,
look for a cat with a long tail because
they jump more, right? The tail is like
it gives them that balance. Monkeys have
a long tail. like tigers, any animal
that has that can jump far, better
jumping, better mousing. So anyway, he
followed my advice and uh then he died
on 911, but that's a whole different
story.
>> Oh my god. Yeah,
>> what a story,
>> you know. I know. But I always thought
about the biting. It's like I mean
that's a horror show. I mean, John, I
had a job in in freshman year on the
docks as a part-time long shoreman and
for two week the first two weeks is
basically the hazing period and they're
like, "Okay, so you have to make prove
yourself." So, I think you'll like this
story. So, the guy So, the my boss, he's
like, "Uh, today go out. Here's a bag.
We poison all the rats." And the rats on
the warf rats are massive giant cats and
but they poison them and then go pick up
the dead ones and throw them in the bag.
I'm like, "All right." So I go out
there, I pick them up by the tail.
>> Oh, dead.
>> Drop them into the into the bag. There's
hundreds of them. And um I picked up one
and it wasn't dead. It whipped around
and bit me like right in the small of my
arm right here. It sunk. It sunk its
teeth and it would not let go. And of
course, as you can imagine, I'm
screaming. I'm all by myself. I gotta
solve this problem myself. So, I bashed
it and bashed it and bashed it against a
a pylon until it let go. And it I was
pleading like all over the place. I go
to the office and the guy's like,
"Teddy, you can go ahead and go home
early." And something told me that
wouldn't be a good idea. So, I just I
was just like, "Okay, I'm I'm like, "No,
I'm good. Just like let me just wrap
myself up. I'll finish my shift." And I
really did need the money. Um I was a
scholarship kid, uh you know, at a at
the second most expensive college in the
country. Uh and I was about to lose all
my financial aid due to the Reagan
budget cuts. So, I needed that money.
So, anyway, the point is I tied I bound
myself up. And uh so the next day when I
came back to work, my boss goes, "You
know, uh if you hadn't if you if you'd
agreed to go home early, I would have
never let you come back."
And I'm like, "You're a real charmer."
But
>> Ted, you must have gone to the hospital.
>> I did. No, I couldn't afford it. Are you
kidding me?
>> Oh my god.
>> I I was always worried that I might, you
know, for like weeks I was like, "What
if I got rabies or
>> Yeah, right.
Whatever rats carry, they carry all
kinds of stuff.
>> No, this is one of the many reasons that
I'm for socialized in the healthcare.
You should be able as a human being to
walk into a clinic and get that taken
care of. It would have cost hundreds of
dollars back in the early 80s. There was
no way I didn't have it.
>> Yeah, healthcare is a human right. I I'm
100% with you. Healthc care is a human
right. It should be free for everybody.
>> And and man, I you know, so for me, when
I think of rats, I always think of that.
And uh you know
it was a tough job.
>> The the test was that you had to carry a
200 pound bag 200 yards. They didn't
care how
>> on your shoulders in front of you. On
your shoulders was the best way. That's
how I did it.
>> Yeah, it's the best way.
>> But it was like that's a lot of weight.
I only weighed like 160 at the time. So,
you know, it was not easy and but the
pay was insane. So it was
>> it had to be.
>> It needed to be. Yeah.
>> Yeah. It was like it was $50 an hour
cash.
>> Cash.
>> No. Yeah. And you went home and the
terrifying thing is you'd go home after
a 12 hour shift with 600 bucks in your
pocket, you know, in on the New York
City subway in 1981.
>> Oh my god. Yeah.
>> You know, you're you're a walking bank.
>> Yeah. Where's Where's Bernie gets when
you need him?
>> Totally. Totally. No, I I I was really
really wanted a gun but couldn't get
one. Um anyway, so with that, um
speaking of gunfire, so we should talk
about this remote junction uh shooting.
So um two, um Palestinians from the West
Bank uh shot and killed uh six Israelis
who were waiting for the bus at remote
junction. Um, how this is covered
depends on the the political um leaning
of the uh of the press organization, but
basically some are saying calling it
Jerusalem, but the truth is it's it's
really occupied territory, right? It's
in
>> Yeah, they keep saying Jerusalem, but
it's in a Jewish settlement in East
Jerusalem,
>> which is the West Bank. It's the
occupied West Bank,
>> which is the West Bank. Correct.
>> Yep. So, um, Emmanuel Macron again in
the news here on Deep Program. And by
the way, please like, follow, and share
the show. Uh, didn't we didn't do the
proper intros this time, but thank you
very much for your support and all that.
>> And thank you to to Chrism ZTC uh with a
question we can get to in a in a second,
but thank you very much for the $5.
>> Yes, thank you indeed. So, yeah, I mean,
so the thing is what do we do? Um I mean
so Macron saying this is another
reminder of why we need to put an end to
the violence and this is all related to
the Gaza war. Um that's I I got to say
what was notable to me was I can't
imagine a year ago that any politician
as mainstream as Emanuel Macron would
ever have been able to say something
like this following a terrorist attack
that it was anything other than just a
cruel horrible event that shouldn't have
happened. and never to tie it into the
Palestinian cause. That's a big change.
>> Yeah, I think it is, too. You're going
to see, you know, the the predictable um
coverage in places like the New York
Post, or or even the the more mainstream
um media like uh the Washington Post,
the New York Times, even the LA Times.
But I I was surprised that Mcronone came
out and and and said what he what he
said. Yeah, I'm a little bit torn over
this because
because
if we're going to
be opposed to attacks on civilians, then
we got to be opposed to attacks on
civilians. At the same time,
um
if if my if my land were were occupied
and my house was taken over by some
strangers from New Jersey who just came
and said, "You you leave now. This is
our house.
>> Yeah.
>> Um I I I don't know what I would do. I
would probably do what these guys did.
They were both shot and killed on on the
scene. Um
and the Israelis, you know, said the
predictable things. Netanyahu went to
the site of the shooting and gave a
speech and but you're right. The bottom
line here is
we all have to work together to not just
end this conflict, but to try to protect
Palestinian human rights because the
Israeli government isn't going to do it.
>> And I don't think the Israeli government
really cares that much about the safety
and security of the Israeli people.
>> I think that's right.
>> Angela, thank you so much for the
donation.
>> Thank you, Angela. Um but do you want to
ask uh do you want to answer uh Chrism
TC?
>> Yeah. Uh Andrew Bamante.
So Andrew
Andrew recently came out with a book in
which he single-handedly,
you know, brought down some mole. Funny
that we never saw any reporting about
any mole in the CIA. Uh but he claims to
have brought down a mole. Uh, he also
went on the Julian Dory podcast and he
uh he waterboarded Julian incorrectly, I
might add.
And I called Julian. I was like, "Dude,
what are you doing? You did it wrong."
And Bamante's got his hair pulled back.
Anyway, so he came out with this book
last week and he says that he took down
this mole and then he says that that he
waterboarded people when he was at the
agency. I don't think any of this is
true.
Andrew Bamante was a targeting analyst
just like his wife. They're both
targeting analysts. And as a targeting
analyst, your job is to go through
thousands and thousands, maybe even
millions of pieces of data to try to
discern the location of a target so that
either your special activities people
can go kill him or kidnap him or your
operations people can go try to recruit
him. Right?
Bamante was not a case officer. He was
not an operations officer. He was what's
called a Sue, a special operations
officer.
Most of the Sue couldn't make it through
operational training. I don't know why
he was a Sue, but most of them just
could not cut the ops ops training. A
Sue then serves as an assistant to the
operations people. So, if I was going to
go do a particularly dangerous meeting,
I would say, "Hey, Andrew, uh, put
together a surveillance team and a
counter surveillance team. I have this
meeting. I'm going to do my surveillance
detection route kickoff at 6:00. The
meeting's at 9. Make sure I don't get
shot." Or at the end of a particularly
long night, I'd say, "Andrew or whoever
the Sue was assigned to me,
I'm tired. I got to do another
surveillance detection route. When you
get back to the embassy, do me a favor
and do my accounting paperwork.
But running around the world catching
moles
and then randomly flying out to secret
sites to waterboard people.
Uh-uh.
No. One thing he's very good at is what
at the agency we used to call SSP,
shameless self-promotion.
M we were taught early on you have to
relentlessly promote yourself as a
Superman because everybody else is
promoting himself as a Superman and
you're competing against these people in
the promotion panels. One thing he's
good at is coming across as Superman.
And if if you're outside the agency and
you're doing it, uh, then it's easy
because
because there's no way anybody can check
your bonafites. All you have to do is
say up, take my word for it, it's
classified,
and then that's it.
>> I'm gonna I'm gonna spontaneously pop
Robbie in because Robbie has something
to say. He wants to just remind people
to follow us over on Rumble and why. And
I think it's frankly just faster to just
have Robbie do it. So Robbie, sorry
about this, but not sorry. Go ahead.
>> Howdy. No, it's uh pretty dog on
mercenary and capitalist. Rumble pays us
more.
>> Yeah.
>> And so if y'all go over to Rumble, if
y'all follow there, Rumble actually pays
John and Ted based on watch hours and
not just the pennies that that YouTube
call pays. So, uh, if you just go over
there, watch them, watch the show over
there. They get paid more and we got to
help John get that house in Greece. So,
let's do it.
>> Thanks. Thanks, Robbie.
>> Yeah. Thanks.
>> All right. I I know like my plan to move
to France is not looking as exciting as
one of the uh chatters pointed out, but
you know, I mean, whatever. France will
as long as the wine is good and the food
is good, which will always be true, uh
everything will be fine. Um, so let's uh
Yeah. Do we wanna do we want to move
over to um Oh, LA. Oh, we are ready for
an ad. Robbie, go ahead and put it up
when you're ready.
>> Yeah, we should do an ad. Yeah.
>> Okay. So, so LA, the Supreme Court um
has deculed the district judge. Uh
basically, the district judge was said
um said, "You guys are ethnically
profiling," which by's own account they
are. Um, and basically, um, the there
are unconstitutional roving patrols sort
of basically going to car washes and
Home Depot, anyone who looks Latino, a
little bit taupe, um, you know, sounds
Spanish, they're they get questioned
about, you know, hey, are you here? Do
you have papers that, you know, prove
that you're legal to be here? Well, the
Supreme Court just basically said they
overturned the lower court decision, but
without comment. Um, and so basically
there's no decision. That to me
indicates that there this is tends to be
for political reasons, right?
>> Yeah.
>> John, while you're chewing on that one,
let me read the ad. Here we go.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, I agree with you.
It's political.
>> You You've probably noticed Rumble is
growing fast and it's not slowing down.
They're building a real alternative to
big tech that puts creators first and
actually protects free speech. And now
there's Rumble Premium. Easy way to
upgrade your experience with Premium.
You get ad free viewing across the
platform. No pre-rolls, no
interruptions, just the content you came
for, plus premium members. Unlock
exclusive content like bonus videos,
behindthe-scene drops, and more from
your favorite creators. Right now,
Rumble is offering $10 off an annual
subscription. Just go to
rumble.com/premium.
Use the promo code studio at checkout.
That's rumble.com/premium.
Promo code studio. No ads, more freedom,
and content you actually care about.
That's the deal. And you can also do it
for $5 and but you'll just be watching
us for just one show. Uh and you
wouldn't see the other stuff. Anyway, so
LA I mean this I mean look I think it's
pretty disgusting. Um you know we've
talked about this before but I think
it's worth mentioning again. you know,
when you're um driving on a freeway near
the Mexico border, or I guess I guess
this would be true uh also anywhere in
Southern California, you may well come
upon a police checkpoint where there's
orange cones and there's uniformed
officers who slow you down, eyeball you,
and they if they see faces that look
like yours or mine, they wave us past.
>> You're good to go. But if you are Latino
looking in their eye, in their minds,
then they pull you over and harass you.
And I don't think that that if that's
constitutional or if that's legal, it
ought not to be. It should be made
illegal.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I I agree. I agree. And to
tell you the truth, Ted, I thought it
was illegal.
>> Maybe we're wrong. Maybe it's state laws
that prohibit cops from doing it. I
don't know. It should be It should be
illegal.
>> I thought Yeah, I thought ethnic
profiling violated the Fourth
Amendment's right um against unlawful
search and seizure because there's no
there's no just cause,
>> right?
>> Yeah. I Yeah, I would. And another
thing, too, is that and this is scary. I
I heard just over the weekend that that
people here in DC have
>> constitutional it's a it's a violation
of the 14th amendment.
>> I thought it was illegal.
>> Protection clause.
>> There it is.
>> Here in DC, people have begun carrying
their passports
just because they're afraid of being
scooped up.
>> Yeah.
>> Um there was a story about
a a violinist for the was it the Salt
Lake City Symphony. He was grabbed and
held for three weeks. The guy's an
American. He was grabbed and held for
three weeks just because just because
they know they can get away with it.
>> Absolutely.
>> So, I don't know. Seriously.
>> Um, we have a question from the YouTube
feed from Jace. Thoughts on Barry Weiss
cashing in with CBS?
>> Oh, you know what? I didn't realize that
it happened. I I'll check it out. Do you
know anything about it?
>> No, I don't know anything.
>> Sorry. Sorry, Jace. All right. Well,
check it out. We'll have to depro that
part of deprogramming will have to await
a night uh tomorrow's show.
>> Yeah,
>> we'll look into that.
>> And definitely.
>> Yeah. And I guess the last big story of
the day, unless something breaks in the
next 10 minutes, is um the school prayer
thing. So, um it's not like um there's
ever been a prohibition against
practicing your religion in school.
You've always been allowed to pray. Um I
was always surprised uh I I only went to
public schools K through 12. Um the I
was always surprised that you could that
prayer groups were allowed on campus as
an after-school activity. U totally okay
to do that. Uh but uh Trump wants to go
further and he wants to promote prayer
in public schools. Uh he says there's
too much anti-religious propaganda in
schools. Obviously we have separation of
church and state. So therefore, you
can't have state sponsored prayer in
schools. John, the part that I want to
talk to you about, and you're a man of
faith, is isn't what's [__] up and
weird to me is not is less the fact that
Trump wants to do this than the fact
that he himself is so brazenly not rel
>> not religious. Not religious in any way.
>> He doesn't there's he doesn't go to
church. No,
>> he doesn't have a spiritual advisor like
many presidents had Billy Graham meet
with them personally.
>> Many Yes.
>> Um it's like he doesn't talk about
scripture. He can't reference it. He
doesn't know. Remember he was asked name
a line from the Bible. One line from the
Bible.
>> Yeah.
>> Couldn't even do Jesus wept. Right.
Couldn't do anything.
>> The the shortest literally the shortest
verse in the entire Bible.
>> Couldn't do one. And Jesus wept,
>> right? And so I mean, you know, this is
I mean, he doesn't know any he's not a
religious man. Nothing wrong with not
being a religious man.
>> No.
>> Beautiful thing. Many Americans are not
religious. But isn't it weird for people
who are Christian to to to think this? I
mean, to see this. I mean, how does he
get away with it with his people? I know
the whole God works in mysterious ways
argument and that like, you know,
evangelicals, some evangelicals think
that, you know, Trump is doing God's
bidding even though he's, you know, even
though he's balls deep in Stormmy
Daniels. I I don't know. I don't get it.
You can you can you explain this to me
at all?
>> I think that he thinks that most
Christians are suckers. I hate to be
cynical like that, but I I believe this.
He thinks most Christians are suckers.
You remember when he walked out of the
White House, there's this near riot
situation. The chairman of the joint ste
chiefs of staff goes out with him and he
goes to St. John's Church, which is
directly across the street from the
White House where every president since
James Madison has gone to services. And
what's he do?
He holds up a Bible
and he just holds it up. Yeah. Upside
down. Later he autographed it.
>> Right. And then on Fox, they started
selling autographs.
>> Only God should be allowed to autograph
the Bible.
>> Yeah.
>> Or his or his kid.
>> But I think that it's an easy and cheap
way to just uh rile up Christians who
are predisposed to support him anyhow.
And he realizes, ah, they're all
suckers. I'm just going to keep doing
this.
I really believe that.
>> I can't Yeah, I I can't argue with that
at all. That sounds right to me. Um, but
but I mean Christians aren't stupid
people.
>> They're no stupider than anyone else
anyway. So, I mean, how is it that I
mean, they they know what's going on.
They know about the grift. I mean, by
the way, thank you MW Knox 186 for the
donation. Much appreciated.
>> Thank you. Thank you.
>> Um, right. I mean, Christians must they
know,
>> don't they? Why don't they hate him for
this?
I would I would be so furious over the
thought that I had been used as as a
political prop
that I would be furious. I don't
understand why
why he's a how he's able to get away
with this.
>> John, this is more for you than for me,
I'm sure. Bees wants to know, can you
speak to the intelligence community's
role in making western western capital
markets accessible to sanctioned groups
via shadow banking?
>> It's a complicated.
>> That's a good that's a good question.
>> Um, and you know, I think a lot of it is
probably still classified,
but think of it this way.
Not only
not only do the interests of the CIA
sometimes diverge from the greater
national interests of the United States,
but they frequently diverge.
I I say all the time in the in that
wonderful Netflix series Narcos, you
know, just as the DEA guys are gonna
swoop in and get Pablo Escobar or
whatever,
>> the CIA station chief throws up.
>> Yeah. He the CIA station chief shows up
and just screws the the whole thing up.
>> Well, the reason that's in the the
series is because that's how it is in
real life. The CIA doesn't really care
what the law is, even what US law is.
And oftentimes the people that they're
dealing with or the governments that
they're dealing with are that are
friendly to the CIA are actually hostile
to the State Department, to the White
House, to US foreign policy.
And so the CIA will arrange
backdoor banking, backdoor investment,
backdoor loans
just to keep these outlaws going.
So often times the CIA is doing
something that is both illegal and
antithetical to American foreign policy.
Somebody also asked at the very
beginning and maybe it was Starion
at the very beginning of the show about
the role of astrology. Has astrology
ever played a role in the CIA's work?
And the answer is yes. It did in the
1950s into the early 1960s as a part of
that overarching MK Ultra program. Like
every bit of craziness that you can come
up with that had the MK Ultra label
attached to it, they tried.
That's insane. Insane. Yeah. Wait, wait.
Time travel.
>> Time travel, teleportation,
>> LSD,
>> all of it. Because they were panicked at
the idea that the Russians were doing it
too, and they were ahead of us.
>> It's a little I mean, is there any link
at all between that and the fact that
just a decade earlier, the Nazis were
also interested in the occult? Yeah,
there is a link because all these people
in positions of authority where they
don't have to report back to the public
and they have unlimited or virtually
unlimited budgets think, you know what,
there's probably nothing to it. But just
in case there is,
and it'll make me a star if it leaks
out.
>> My father told me about the wackiest
classified story. He had told me about a
bunch of them, but I'm sure this is no
longer declarified
because it's so old. But apparently,
John, maybe you know about this, but
apparently the Air Force was interested
in insect mutations
>> and uh as part of a cold war, and they
wanted to see if they could make bugs
like house flies, giant size,
>> and and the plan was to like drop 10
10inch house flies on the Soviet Union.
And I was like, "So what exactly did
they think would happen?" And he said,
"Well, we hadn't thought it through that
much." See,
>> and basically we thought that like, and
I'm like, "So what? So if we drop the
10-in house flies on the Russians, then
nobody goes outside anymore and our
troops can just march into Moscow." And
he's like, "Maybe, I don't know." And
he's like I'm like, "Why wouldn't the
Russians just go out with bats and
tennis rackets and have a great time?"
Also, what's going to stop these flies
from coming to the United States?
>> Exactly.
>> I don't know. And so so he said he
claimed that they actually had some
success because insects, you know, they
have very short lifespan. So you can
have thousands of generations in a very
short time. Yes. And he said the
problem, of course, was he could get
them to be pretty big, but they would
hatch and immediately collapse upon
themselves because the exoskeleton
wasn't meant to like scale up to that
size. So basically, they would hatch and
collapse in a in a Jewy gelatinous mass.
And I'm like, "Is is there video?" And
he was like, "There's film." I'm like,
"I want to see it, but
>> oh my god."
>> Your text.
>> What kind of people are we?
>> Oh my god.
>> [__] idiots. Meanwhile, people
literally I couldn't have, you know, I
couldn't go to the doctor for my rat
bite.
>> Yeah.
>> But, you know, but that's where our
money is going.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Oh my god.
>> Um Oh, yeah. Yeah. uh your little
dialectical boo on Rumble saying I might
remember that they tried to put an
antenna in a house cat and don't forget
the Russians had had a spy beluga.
>> They Oh, the spy beluga actually like
transmitted data back to them. Um
>> and there are and there's spy there spy
dolphins and corpuses, right?
>> Yeah, that's right. And pigeons, you
know, we we trained pigeons for years to
land on the window sills of the Soviet
embassy here in Washington
>> just to pick up vibrations from that was
the problem. They land on the window
sill and they're couping and it screws
up the sound.
>> And then there's the And then there's
the uh Havana syndrome, right? Probably
a
>> Oh yeah. Oh my god. Hav I I I curse
whoever implemented Havana syndrome
because my phone rings off the freaking
hook from people who have Havana
syndrome. And you know for so long I
thought ah well it's probably just a nut
until friends of mine started getting it
and now I have to be I'm I'm actually a
believer in Havana syndrome.
>> So you think that that you think this
was a Cuban or whatever attempt to
>> or American or Chinese? Yeah. I I don't
think it was the Cubans. Yeah, I don't.
And I'll tell you why. Because when the
story
>> They denied it like
>> when the story first broke, I was in
Cuba. I happened to be in Cuba and the
Cubans made a huge production out of
saying we will open the books. We will
open the the files. We'll work with the
Americans and give them everything that
they ask for. And that just told me that
no, this isn't
>> Campbell on YouTube is reminding us,
wasn't Nancy Reagan influenced into the
war on drugs by an astrologologist?
>> Yes, very much so.
>> By the way, speaking of astrology, we
now learn that the due to the rotation
of the earth, u we know that actually
like all of our signs are off by about
one sign from when they were conceived
2,000 years ago. So like I think I'm a
Virgo, but actually I'm a Leo.
[Laughter]
Oh my god.
So they that's probably what went wrong
with Nancy Reagan and the war on drugs.
The astrologer was just off by roughly
9%.
>> Wow. Okay. I'll tell you what, today is
an unusually clear day. There's not much
uh humidity. It's going to be clear all
night. It also happens to be one day
after the brightest orange moon of the
year. So, I'm going to go out there with
my telescope.
>> Why is it orange?
>> Um, it's just the position of the of the
sun behind behind the Earth if you're on
the east coast and it's nighttime.
>> It's just one of those things. It
happens once a year. And so, here it is.
So, in China, I think it's in China, um
there's a a lunar eclipse last night or
was a lunar eclipse last night. So, I'm
going to try and get some pictures
tonight.
>> All right. Sounds good. Yeah. For people
who aren't familiar, John, you have a uh
ast what do what we call this?
Astronomical photography.
>> Is that Yeah. Yeah. Astronomical
photography. I've been putting them on
Facebook as I do them and they're good.
>> Getting better and better. Thank you.
Thank you. I appreciate it. It's fun.
It's time consuming. I always look at
them.
>> Thanks very much.
>> Um, so you have to do like long
exposures, right?
>> Yeah. Long exposure. Yeah. And and for
people who know me personally, they know
that I have an utterly irrational fear
of mosquitoes.
And um, so it's hard for me to sit out
there at night for two hours dealing
with mosquitoes. I freaking hate it.
But, you know, we all have our cross to
bear. That's really funny. Uh yeah. Um
>> you know, one other thing. The night
that we captured up as a beta,
>> um there were mosquitoes all over the
hospital and I I was freaked out by them
because I couldn't take the
chloricquin because um it gave me such
terrible nightmares. So, I just stopped
taking the chloricquin, which prevents
malaria once the malarial mosquito
>> bites you. So, I'm just taking my my
chances with the mosquito. I go into Abu
Zubeda's room to wait for him to come
out of surgery and it's like a cloud of
mosquitoes in there. I'm like, great.
So, I put the ceiling fan on high blast
and this was March. It was a little bit
cold, you know? So, I'm sitting there
like this. I'm freezing and this FBI
agent comes in. He goes, "Dude, it's
freezing in here. What are you doing?" I
said, "I would rather freeze to death
than be bitten by a Pakistani mosquito.
Not going to happen tonight.
>> By the way, I assume you know this
following factoid, right? But mosquitoes
will not fly if it's over 64 degrees.
>> I did not know that. And it's going to
be in the high 50s tonight. Okay.
>> You're safe.
>> Thank you, Ted.
>> You're welcome. And with that, uh, thank
you again everyone for joining us. Uh,
today's Monday, September 8th. Tomorrow
we'll be back Tuesday 5:00 Eastern time
as we are Monday through Friday here on
Drogram with me Ted R and John Kuryaku
and we appreciate your donations. Please
like, follow, and share the show. As
producer Robbie uh indicated it is best
for us if you can watch us on Rumble. So
what a lot of people are doing who
aren't really that excited about Rumble
is they they watch us sort of
simultaneously. They just have the
Rumble run in the background and they
watch us on YouTube. that works. You
know,
>> we're actually we're actually able to
make a go of this thanks to you guys
watching on Rumble. It's it's that
important. Thank you.
>> Star Lion is saying astrology still
works ignoring the constellations
because it's really more about the
seasons or something earth related and
not star related.
>> All right. Okay. I don't I mean know the
lunar movements I mean obviously affects
tides and all that. That has to be that
has to affect things. And cops swear by
the idea of the full moon stuff.
>> Yeah.
>> So, more crime, more weirdness on full
during full moons.
>> I think it's just because you can see
better and weirdos can don't need a
flashlight. But what do I know?
>> All right, guys. Um anyway, uh let Oh my
god, what am I doing here? Why do I not
have this?
Okay. All right.
There we go.
>> Great. Thank you.
[Music]